https://www.ectopic.org.uk/privacy-policy/

020 7733 2653contact usDonateForumsSupporting people who have experienced an early pregnancy complication and the health care professionals who care for them
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.What information do we collect about you?We collect information about you when you contact us, make an enquiry, request or use our services/information, or purchase an item from our online shop. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete surveys and provide feedback. Website usage information is collected using cookies.How will we use the information about you?We collect information about you to respond to your query or request or use our services/information, process your order (if using our online shop) and, if you agree, to email you about other services and activities of the charity we think may be of interest to you. We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website.We will not share your information for marketing purposes with other organisations. In processing your shop order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.MarketingWe would like to send you information about our services and activities of ours and other organisations with which we work about early pregnancy which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other organisations. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please contact us using the email address below.Access to your information and correctionYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us using the email address below. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.CookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is anonymised and used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information, visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some, of our website features may not function as a result.Other websitesOur website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.Changes to our privacy policyWe keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page.This privacy policy was last updated on 16 May 2018.How to contact usPlease contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you by emailing us at: ept@ectopic.org.uk.Comments are closed.Contact usThe Ectopic Pregnancy Trust 483 Green Lanes London N13 4BS For letter correspondence only. If you need to send a parcel/package, please contact us for an alternative address.Phone Helpline:
020 7733 2653 Arrange a call-backAdministration & Press:
020 7096 1838 ept@ectopic.org.ukReg. Charity: 1071811News George Runs an Amazing V40 Marathon Paula Takes to the Skies to Raise Funds and Awareness The EPT Christmas Cards and E-Cards A Chance Encounter – The Power of Awareness Charlie is Supporting us with her amazing Forget Me Not Bath Bomb RangeTake part in our research studyWe are investigating the the emotional impact of an ectopic pregnancy. We are also interested in the support you would have found helpful from the health service or independent sector. Knowledge gained from this study will help support other women and shape service delivery.Take the surveyForumsShopSkype supportDonateVolunteerTranslate Google Translate is an automatic translation service that uses technology, not human translators, to translate text. By linking to this tool to facilitate translations, we hope to make information available to visitors for whom English may not be their first language. Please be aware that as translations are through technology, they may not be perfect. The EPT does not own, manage or control any aspect of Google Translate and is not responsible for the translations provided by Google Translate. The EPT does not make any guarantees as to the accuracy, reliability, or timeliness of the translations provided.
Subscribe to our email newsletterEmail Address
Etopic is The Ectopic Pregnancy Trust's regular e-newsletter, with insights into the work we do, the charity's activities and how we provide support, raise awareness and support research into ectopic pregnancy. Read our previous newsletters »
